Historic Image Collection HIC
Stage
- Private Schools - Gunston School for Girls
- Private Schools - Hamilton Institute
- Private Schools - Hawthorne
- Private Schools - Holton-Arms
- Private Schools - Holy Cross Academy
- Private Schools - Immaculata Junior College
- Private Schools - King-Smith Studio
- Private Schools - Lucy Webb Hayes National Training School
- Private Schools - Madeira School
- Private Schools - Maret
- Private Schools - Martha Washington Seminary
- Private Schools - Misses Kerr's Home
- Private Schools - National Cathedral School for Girls
- Private Schools - National Catholic Service School for Women
- Private Schools - National Craft Training School
- Private Schools - National Park Seminary
- Private Schools - National Training School for Boys
- Private Schools - Rittenhouse Academy
- Private Schools - Saint Alban's School for Boys
- Private Schools - Saint Aloysius
- Private Schools - Saint John's College High School
- Private Schools - Sidwell Friend
- Private Schools - University School
- Private Schools - Visitation
- Private Schools - Washington College for Young Ladies
- Private Schools - Washington Seminary
- Private Schools - Washington School for Secretaries
- Private Schools - Washington School of Physical Education
- Private Schools - Wayland Seminary
- Private Schools - Woodward School for Boys
- Public Health Centers
- Public Libraries
  See Also: World War II - War Drives; See Also: Biography - Groups; See Also: Biography - N (Noyes)
- Public Libraries - General
- Public Libraries - Anacostia
- Public Libraries - Central
- Public Libraries - Cleveland Park
- Public Libraries - Fort Davis
- Public Libraries - Francis Gregory
- Public Libraries - Georgetown
- Public Libraries - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial
- Public Libraries - Mt. Pleasant
- Public Libraries - New York Avenue
- Public Libraries - Northeast
- Public Libraries - Palisades
- Public Libraries - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Public Libraries - Petworth
- Public Libraries - Southeast
- Public Libraries - Southwest
- Public Libraries - Takoma Park
- Public Libraries - Tenley
- Public Libraries - Watha T. Daniel
- Public Schools
- Public Schools - General
- Elementary
- Public Schools - Elementary - Abbott
- Public Schools - Elementary - Adams
- Public Schools - Elementary - Anacostia
- Public Schools - Elementary - Benning
- Public Schools - Elementary - Berret
- Public Schools - Elementary - Blake
- Public Schools - Elementary - Blow
- Public Schools - Elementary - Bradley
- Public Schools - Elementary - Brown
- Public Schools - Elementary - Bunker-Hill
- Public Schools - Elementary - Cardoza
- Public Schools - Elementary - Chevy Chase
- Public Schools - Elementary - Cook
- Public Schools - Elementary - Cooke
- Public Schools - Elementary - Corcoran
- Public Schools - Elementary - Crummell
- Public Schools - Elementary - Dennison
- Public Schools - Elementary - Draper
- Public Schools - Elementary - Eastern
- Public Schools - Elementary - Emery
- Public Schools - Elementary - First Lancasterian
- Public Schools - Elementary - Force
- Public Schools - Elementary - Fort Reno
- Public Schools - Elementary - Franklin
- Public Schools - Elementary - Gage
- Public Schools - Elementary - Gales
- Public Schools - Elementary - Garfield
- Public Schools - Elementary - Hardy
- Public Schools - Elementary - High Street
- Public Schools - Elementary - Hillsdale
- Public Schools - Elementary - Jackson Street
- Public Schools - Elementary - Johnson
- Public Schools - Elementary - Ketcham
- Public Schools - Elementary - Lafayette
- Public Schools - Elementary - Langston
- Public Schools - Elementary - Lincoln
- Public Schools - Elementary - Logan
- Public Schools - Elementary - Lovejoy
- Public Schools - Elementary - Ludlow
- Public Schools - Elementary - March
- Public Schools - Elementary - McCormick
- Public Schools - Elementary - Park View
- Public Schools - Elementary - Patterson
- Public Schools - Elementary - Peabody
- Public Schools - Elementary - Perry
- Public Schools - Elementary - Potomac
- Public Schools - Elementary - Reno
- Public Schools - Elementary - Simmons
- Public Schools - Elementary - Slater
- Public Schools - Elementary - Sumner
- Public Schools - Elementary - Syphax
- Public Schools - Elementary - Takoma
- Public Schools - Elementary - Thomas
- Public Schools - Elementary - Thompson
- Public Schools - Elementary - Thomson
- Public Schools - Elementary - Threlkeld
- Public Schools - Elementary - Turner
- Public Schools - Elementary - Tyler
- Public Schools - Elementary - Wallach
- Public Schools - Elementary - Webster
- Public Schools - Elementary - West
- Public Schools - Elementary - Western
- Public Schools - Elementary - Wheatley
- Public Schools - Elementary - Woodridge
- Public Schools - Elementary - Young
- High School
- Public Schools - High School - General
- Public Schools - High School - Anacostia
- Public Schools - High School - Armstrong
- Public Schools - High School - Cardozo
- Public Schools - High School - Central
- Public Schools - High School - Coolidge
- Public Schools - High School - Dunbar
- Public Schools - High School - Eastern
- Public Schools - High School - M Street
- Public Schools - High School - McKinley
- Public Schools - High School - Washington
- Public Schools - High School - Western
- Public Schools - High School - Wilson
- Junior High School
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Deal
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Gordon
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Hine
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Jefferson
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Kramer
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Lincoln
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Randall
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Portable Schoolhouses
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Sport
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Teachers and Officials
- Public Schools - Junior High School - Vocational
- Pumping Station
  See: Water Supply
- Radio and Television
- Rayburn Office Building
  See: House Office Building
- Railroads
- Red Cross
- Redskins, Washington
- Reformatories
- Rent Control
- Republican Capitol Hill Club
- Reservoirs
  See Also: Water Supply
- Residential Sections
- Residential Sections - Adams Morgan
- Residential Sections - Anacostia
- Residential Sections - Chinatown
- Residential Sections - Columbia Heights
- Residential Sections - Foggy Bottom
- Residential Sections - Georgetown
- Residential Sections - Southeast
- Residential Sections - Southwest
- Residential Sections - Tenley
- Restaurants
  See Also: Residential Sections - Chinatown
- RFK Stadium
  See: Stadiums
- Riots
- Rock Creek Park
  See: Parks; See: Mills; See: Streets - Rock Creek Parkway
- Rowing
  See: Boats and Boating; See: Sports
- Saloons
- Salvation Army
- Scottish Rite Temple
- Seals and Symbols
- Senate Office Buildings
- Senators, Washington
- Sesquicentennial
- Settlement Houses
- Sewage Disposal
- Slums
  See: Housing
- Smithsonian Institution
  See Also: Museums; See Also: Tiber Creek; See Also: Zoo
- Smithsonian Institution - American History
- Smithsonian Institution - Castle Building
- Smithsonian Institution - Exhibits
- Smithsonian Institution - Freer Gallery of Art
  See Also: Art Galleries - Freer
- Smithsonian Institution - Grounds
- Smithsonian Institution - National Museum (Arts and Industry)
- Smithsonian Institution - Natural History
- Snow
- Soap Box Derby
- Social Life
- Social Planning
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations
- Soldiers, Sailors and Marines Club
- Soldiers Home
  See Also: Houses - Anderson House
- Southeast
- Southwest
- Spanish-American War
  See Also: Arlington Cemetery - Monuments
- Sports
  See Also: Boats and Boating; See Also: Stadiums; See Also: Tidal Basin
- Stadiums
- Stage Coach
- Standards, Bureau of
- Starplex
  See: Armory
- State Department
- State, War and Navy Building
  See Also: War Department
- States
- Stores
- Stores - General
- Stores - Garfinckel's
- Stores - Hecht Company
- Stores - Kann's
- Stores - Lansburgh
- Stores - Peoples Drug Store
- Stores - Reeds
- Stores - Rich's
- Stores - Scan
- Stores - Woodward and Lothrop
- Streetcars
- Street Cleaners
- Street Railroads
  See Also: Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue; See Also: Strikes; See Also: Transportation
- Street Signs
- Street Vendors
- Streets
  See Also: Floods; See Also: Funerals; See Also: Houses; See Also: Parades
- Streets - General
- Streets - 1st Street
- Streets - 3rd Street
- Streets - 4th Street (includes 4 ½ Street)
- Streets - 5th Street
- Streets - 7th Street
- Streets - 8th Street
- Streets - 9th Street
- Streets - 10th Street
- Streets - 11th Street
- Streets - 12th Street
- Streets - 13th Street
- Streets - 14th Street
- Streets - 15th Street
- Streets - 16th Street
- Streets - 17th Street
- Streets - 18th Street
- Streets - 19th Street
- Streets - 20th Street
- Streets - 21st Street
- Streets - 23rd Street
- Streets - 24th Street
- Streets - 31st Street
- Streets - 32nd Street
- Streets - 33rd Street
- Streets - 34th Street
- Streets - 35th Street
- Streets - A Street
- Streets - B Street
- Streets - Calvert Street
- Streets - Canal Street
- Streets - Cathedral Avenue
- Streets - Columbia Road
- Streets - Conduit Road
- Streets - Connecticut Avenue
- Streets - Constitution Avenue
- Streets - D Street
- Streets - Davenport Street
- Streets - Dennison Place
- Streets - E Street
- Streets - East Capitol Street
- Streets - East Executive Avenue
- Streets - Eye Street
  See: I Street
- Streets - F Street
  See Also: World War II - VJ Day
- Streets - Florida Avenue
- Streets - Freeway, Inner Loop
- Streets - Freeway, Southwest
- Streets - G Street
- Streets - George Washington Memorial Parkway
- Streets - Georgia Avenue
- Streets - H Street
- Streets - Harvard Street
- Streets - I Street
- Streets - Independence Avenue
- Streets - Indiana Avenue
- Streets - Irving
- Streets - Jackson Place
- Streets - Jefferson Place
- Streets - K Street
- Streets - Kansas Avenue
- Streets - Kilbourne Street
- Streets - L Street
- Streets - Lamont Street
- Streets - Louisiana Avenue
- Streets - M Street
- Streets - MacArthur Boulevard
- Streets - Madison Place
- Streets - Maine Avenue
- Streets - Market Space
- Streets - Maryland Avenue
- Streets - Massachusetts Avenue
- Streets - Missouri Avenue
- Streets - Mount Vernon Memorial Highway
  See: George Washington Memorial Parkway
- Streets - N Street
- Streets - Nebraska Avenue
- Streets - New Hampshire Avenue
- Streets - New Jersey Avenue
- Streets - New York Avenue
- Streets - Newark Street
- Streets - North Capitol Street
- Streets - O Street
- Streets - Ohio Avenue
- Streets - Ohio Drive
- Streets - P Street
- Streets - Park Road
- Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue
  See Also: Treasury Department; See Also: Triangle; See Also: Visitors; See Also: Weather
- Streets - Q Street
- Streets - R Street
- Streets - Rhode Island Avenue
- Streets - Riverside Drive
- Streets - Rock Creek Parkway
- Streets - S Street
- Streets - Schott Alley
- Streets - South Capitol Street
- Streets - Southeast/Southwest Freeway
- Streets - T Street
- Streets - Terrace Court
- Streets - Treasury Place
- Streets - U Street
- Streets - V Street
- Streets - Van Ness Street
- Streets - Vermont Avenue
- Streets - Virginia Avenue
- Streets - Water Street
- Streets - West Executive Avenue
- Streets - West Leg
- Streets - Western Avenue
- Streets - Whitehurst Freeway
- Streets - Wisconsin Avenue
- Streets - Woodland Drive
- Strikes
- Subways
- Suffrage
  See Also: Parades - Suffrage; See Also: Biography - M (Mussey)
- Supreme Court
- Swimming
  See: Sports; See: Tidal Basin
- Swimming Pools
- Synagogues
- Taft Memorial
- Takoma Park
- Tariff Commission
- Taxi Cabs
  See: Strikes; See: Transportation
- Telephone
- Television and Film
  See Also: Radio and Television
- Temperance Fountain
- Temporary Buildings
  See: World War II - Temporary Building; See: Navy Department; See: Views
- Tenley
- Theatres
- Theatres - Academia
- Theatres - Academy of Music
- Theatres - Albaugh's Grand Opera House
- Theatres - Arena Stage
- Theatres - Belasco
- Theatres - Bijou
- Theatres - Burlesque
- Theatres - Calvert
- Theatres - Carter Barron Amphitheater
- Theatres - Chase's
- Theatres - Columbia
- Theatres - Criterion
- Theatres - Cyclorama
- Theatres - Earle
- Theatres - Fords
- Theatres - Grover
- Theatres - Keith's
- Theatres - Knickerbocker
- Theatres - National
- Theatres - Palace
- Theatres - Pix
- Theatres - Rialto
- Theatres - Stage Door Canteen
  See Also: World War II - Service Clubs
- Theatres - Stand
- Theatres - Takoma Park
- Theatres - Tivoli
- Theodore Roosevelt Island
- Tiber Creek
- Tidal Basin
  See Also: Parks; See Also: Trees - Cherry; See Also: Views
- Tornadoes
  See Also: Streets - A Street; See Also: Weather
- Tourists
  See Also: Transportation; See Also: Trees - Cherry
- Traffic
- Transportation
  See Also: Strikes
- Treasury Department
- Tree House
  See: Houses
- Trees
  See Also: Parks; See Also: Capitol
- General
- Cherry
- Dogwood
- Magnolia
- Tulip
- Trials
- Triangle
  See Also: Post Office; See Also: Archives, National; See Also: Apex Building; See Also: Federal Trade Commission; See Also: Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Tudor Place
  See: Houses - 31st Street
- Tunnels
- Union Station
  See Also: Fountains; See Also: Strikes; See Also: Visitors; See Also: Subways; See Also: World War II - Soldiers/Servicemen
- University Club
- Van Ness Mansion
- Van Ness Mausoleum
  See: Cemeteries - Oak Hill
- Veterans Administration
- Veterans Day
- Vietnam War Demonstrations
- Views
- Views - General/Undated
- Views - 1750 - 1799
- Views - 1800 - 1819
- Views - 1820 - 1839
- Views - 1840 - 1859
- Views - 1860 - 1879
- Views - 1880 - 1899
- Views - 1900 - 1919
- Views - 1920 - 1939
- Views - 1940 - 1959
- Views - 1960 - 1979
- Views - 1980 - 1999
- Visitation Convent
  See: Private Schools
- Visitors
- Voting Rights
  See: Suffrage
- War Department
  See Also: Pentagon
- War of 1812
- Washington Auditorium
- Washington Board of Trade
- Washington Boy's Club
- Washington Channel
- Washington Gas Light Company
  See: Gas Company
- Washington Home for Incurables
  See: Old Age Homes
- Washington Monument
  See: Memorials - Washington, George (Monument); See: Tidal Basin
- Water Gate Concerts
  See: Music - Watergate Concerts
- Water Supply
  See Also: Reservoirs
- Waterfront
  See Also: Boats and Boating; See Also: Potomac River; See Also: Views
- Weather
- Weather Bureau
- White House
  See Also: Fountains; See Also: Tiber Creek; See Also: Presidents of the United States; See Also: War of 1812; See Also: Weather
- White House - Exterior - East Wing
- White House - Exterior - North Front
- White House - Exterior - South Front
- White House - Exterior - West Wing/Executive Offices
- White House - Exterior - Gates
- White House - Exterior - Grounds
- East Wing
- North Front
- South Front
- West Wing/Executive Offices
- Gates
- Grounds
- Interior
- White House - Interior - General
- White House - Interior - Bedrooms
- White House - Interior - Blue Room
- White House - Interior - Cabinet Room
- White House - Interior - Conservatory
- White House - Interior - Corridors
- White House - Interior - Dining Rooms
- White House - Interior - Diplomatic Reception Room
- White House - Interior - East Room
- White House - Interior - Executive Office/Oval Office
- White House - Interior - Furniture
- White House - Interior - Green Room
- White House - Interior - Kitchen
- White House - Interior - Library
- White House - Interior - Lincoln Bedroom
- White House - Interior - North Vestibule
- White House - Interior - Red Room
- White House - Interior - Remodeling
- White House - Interior - Secretary's/Clerk's Office
- White House - Interior - Sitting Room
- White House - Interior - Swimming Pool
- White House - Interior - Pets
- White House - Interior - People/Visitors
- White House - Interior - Stables
- Wilson Building
- Women
- Woodward and Lothrop
  See: Stores - Woodward and Lothrop
- World War I
  See Also: Days, Special; See Also: Memorials - World War I; See Also: Parades - World War I; See Also: Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations
- World War II
- World War II - General
- World War II - Bonds
- World War II - Children
- World War II - Civil Defense
- World War II - Draft
- World War II - National Youth Administration
- World War II - Rationing
- World War II - Scrap Drives
- World War II - Service Clubs
- World War II - Soldiers/Servicemen
- World War II - Temporary Buildings
  See Also: Navy Department; See Also: Parades - World War II
- World War II - VJ Day
- World War II - War Drives
- World War II - Women
- YMCA
- Zoo
- 4th of July
- Accidents
- Adams Morgan
- Advertising
- Aerial Views
- Agriculture, Department of
- AIDS Quilt
- Air and Space Museum, National
- Air Raid Shelters
- Airplanes
- Airports
- Airports - General
- Airports - Dulles Airport
- Airports - National Airport
- Airships
- Alexandria, Virginia
- Alleys
- American Art, Museum of
- American Association of University Women
- American Federation of Labor
- American History Museum, National
- American Legion Building
- American Pharmaceutical Building
- American Red Cross
- Anacostia
- Anacostia Community Museum
- Anacostia River (and Eastern Branch)
- Analostan Island
- Anderson Cottage
- Apartment Houses
- Apex Building
- Aqueducts
- Arboretum
- Archives, National
- Arlington, Virginia
- Arlington National Cemetery
- Arlington National Cemetery - General
- Arlington National Cemetery - Amphitheater
- Arlington National Cemetery - Arlington House
- Arlington National Cemetery - Civil War Unknown Tomb
- Arlington National Cemetery - Confederate Monument
- Arlington National Cemetery - L'Enfant Tomb
- Arlington National Cemetery - Maine Memorial
- Arlington National Cemetery - Memorials
- Arlington National Cemetery - Temple of Fame
- Arlington National Cemetery - Tomb of the Unknown
- Armistice Day
- Armory
- Army and Navy Club
- Army War College
- Arsenal
- Art Exhibits
- Art Galleries
- Art Galleries - Corcoran
- Art Galleries - Freer
- Art Galleries - National Gallery of Art
- Art Galleries - Phillips
- Arts and Industry Museum Building
- Associations
- Automobile
- Aviation
- Aviation - General
- Aviation - Langley Aerodrome
- Aviation - Wright Brothers
- Banks
- Banks - American National
- Banks - Brightwood Savings
- Banks - Bank of Columbia
- Banks - Central National
- Banks - Citizens National
- Banks - Columbia National
- Banks - District National
- Banks - Farmers and Mechanics National
- Banks - Federal American National
- Banks - First Federal Savings and Loan
- Banks - Freedman's Savings
- Banks - Lincoln National
- Banks - National Bank of Washington
- Banks - National Metropolitan
- Banks - National Safe Deposit
- Banks - National Savings
- Banks - Riggs
- Banks - Second National
- Banks - Union Trust
- Banks - Washington Loan and Trust
- Banks - Washington Savings
- Bars
- Barges
  See: Canals - CandO Canal
- Barthodi Fountain
- Baseball
- Basketball
- Bethesda Naval Center
- Bicycles and Bicycling
- Big Brothers
- Black History Month
- Blacks
- Bladensburg, Maryland
- Blimps
- Board of Trade
- Boats and Boating
- Bonus Army/Bonus March
- Books and Book Sellers
- Botanic Garden
- Boundary Stones
- Boy Scouts
- Boys' Club
- Braddock's Rock
- Bridges
- Bridges - General
- Bridges - 9th Street
- Bridges - 11th Street
- Bridges - 14th Street (Rochambeau)
- Bridges - 16th Street
- Bridges - Agriculture, Department of
- Bridges - Anacostia
- Bridges - Aqueduct
- Bridges - Arlington Memorial
- Bridges - Benning Road
- Bridges - C and O Canal
- Bridges - Cabin John
- Bridges - Calvert Street
- Bridges - Capital Beltway
- Bridges - Chain Bridge
- Bridges - Dumbarton
- Bridges - East Capitol Street
- Bridges - Georgetown Bridge
- Bridges - H Street Bridge
- Bridges - Independence Avenue
- Bridges - K Street
- Bridges - Key, Francis Scott Bridge
- Bridges - Klingle Bridge
- Bridges - Long Bridge
- Bridges - M Street
- Bridges - Massachusetts Avenue
- Bridges - Monroe Street
- Bridges - New York Avenue
- Bridges - Park Road
- Bridges - Pedestrian
- Bridges - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Bridges - Piney Branch
- Bridges - Railroad
- Bridges - Reflecting Pool
- Bridges - Rochambeau
- Bridges - Rock Creek Park
- Bridges - Roosevelt, Theodore
- Bridges - Sousa, John Phillip
- Bridges - South Capitol Street
- Bridges - T Street
- Bridges - Taft, William Howard
- Bridges - Three Sisters Bridge
- Bridges - Tidal Basin
- Bridges - Tunnicliffe
- Bridges - Washington Channel
- Bridges - Wilson, Woodrow
- Bridges - Wisconsin Avenue
- Brightwood Race Track
- Building Associations
- Buildings and Offices
- Buildings and Offices - General
- Buildings and Offices - Acacia Mutual
- Buildings and Offices - Albee
- Buildings and Offices - American Automobile Association
- Buildings and Offices - American Building
- Buildings and Offices - American Federation of Labor
- Buildings and Offices - Arlington Building
- Buildings and Offices - Arts Club
- Buildings and Offices - Atlantic Building
- Buildings and Offices - Bliss Building
- Buildings and Offices - Bond Building
- Buildings and Offices - Census, Bureau of
- Buildings and Offices - Chamber of Commerce
- Buildings and Offices - Coast Guard
- Buildings and Offices - Colorado Building
- Buildings and Offices - Commercial Bank
- Buildings and Offices - Cornwell, C.C. Building
- Buildings and Offices - Customs House
- Buildings and Offices - Davidson Building
- Buildings and Offices - Department of Education
- Buildings and Offices - Department of Energy
- Buildings and Offices - Dove Building
- Buildings and Offices - Equitable Building
- Buildings and Offices - Farragut Building
- Buildings and Offices - Federal Storage Company
- Buildings and Offices - Fendall Building
- Buildings and Offices - Firemen's Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Forest Industries
- Buildings and Offices - Forrestal Building
- Buildings and Offices - Franklin Fire Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Fulton
- Buildings and Offices - Glover Building
- Buildings and Offices - Government Heating Plant
- Buildings and Offices - Hoe Building
- Buildings and Offices - Home Builders
- Buildings and Offices - Homer Building
- Buildings and Offices - Insurance Building
- Buildings and Offices - International Club
- Buildings and Offices - Jordan Piano Company
- Buildings and Offices - Kellogg Building
- Buildings and Offices - Kiplinger Editors Building
- Buildings and Offices - Labor, Department of
- Buildings and Offices - Lafayette Building
- Buildings and Offices - Lemon Building
- Buildings and Offices - Liberty Loan Building
- Buildings and Offices - Lord Memorial Hall
- Buildings and Offices - Machinists Building
- Buildings and Offices - Maltry Building
- Buildings and Offices - Manhattan Coffee Mills
- Buildings and Offices - McShain Building
- Buildings and Offices - Methodist Building
- Buildings and Offices - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade
- Buildings and Offices - Mills Building
- Buildings and Offices - Montgomery Building
- Buildings and Offices - Moses Building
- Buildings and Offices - Munsey Building
- Buildings and Offices - National Defense Building
- Buildings and Offices - National Palace
- Buildings and Offices - National Press Club
- Buildings and Offices - Norris Building
- Buildings and Offices - Pennsylvania Building
- Buildings and Offices - People's Mutual Benefit Insurance Co.
- Buildings and Offices - Potomac Electric Power Company
- Buildings and Offices - Presidential Building
- Buildings and Offices - Real Estate Title Insurance Company
- Buildings and Offices - Reconstruction Finance Corporation
- Buildings and Offices - Riggs Building
- Buildings and Offices - Riggs Fire Insurance
- Buildings and Offices - Sanders and Stayman
- Buildings and Offices - Shoreham
- Buildings and Offices - Southern Railway
- Buildings and Offices - Standard Oil Company